It’s not too bad here.
Let’s just close the door.
So I
I opened this box, right?
Yeah?
The box was hollow inside.
And there was this ghostly face right there.
Even the face was pale
and it was just lying there, then boom, it stood up.
I think that’s when the seeker started moving.
I think I woke the seeker up.
No wonder something felt off over there.
There was all this fog rolling in too.
Think we can hide here?
The game's starting.
Let’s hide.
Let’s just stay hidden for a few minutes, man.
I was just...
That must’ve been really scary.
Dude, I swear
I was so shocked.
“Hide-and-seek starts now.”
“You have 4,444 seconds to hide.”
“If the seeker spots you”
“you’ll be locked up immediately.”
[If most of you survive, the Treasure Maker fandom will receive the grand prize]
Hey, we have to survive no matter what.
So we
- Yeah?
- we need to run from now on.
From now on
We gotta do something.
From now on, for Treasure Maker.
Okay.
We’ll make it out in one piece.
Okay bro, see you when we make it out.
Ready or not, here I come
Maybe one of us should’ve hidden in there.
Inside the wardrobe?
Should we?
When the seeker’s checking another room, we’ll leave.
He’s coming to check this room now.
He glanced in here.
Really?
Yeah!
Haruto, let’s move somewhere else.
Wanna sneak around and find keys without getting caught?
Sure thing.
Right?
We do need keys anyway.
Also, it's
just the two of us.
- Two people can team up.
- Whoa you scared me.
Let’s go now.
Sure, let’s go.
We need plenty of keys.
Haruto
let’s change places.
we gotta move.
They’ll probably come check here soon.
Let’s go to that room over there.
The seeker
seems to be a woman.
I can hear heels, that click clacking.
The clacking
of high heels.
Someone in high heels.
[The Seeker is heading to the basement]
[Seeker / Basement / Yoshi / Hyunsuk / The sound of the Seeker's footsteps]
Where are you headed?
Where are you going?
Treasure Maker, I'm safe.
I have to find a key fast.
This is so scary.
Seriously scary.
This is so scary, seriously scary.
[Seeker reappears on the second floor]
[At the same time / Junnghwan's on the move]
[Second floor / Seeker / Junghwan]
[Calmly assessing the situation outside]
[Somewhere close to Jaehyuk and Doyoung / 2F / Doyoung / Jaehyuk / Seeker / Junghwan]
Here it is.
I already searched overe here and didn't find anything.
[They hear the Seeker's footsteps]
[Second floor / Doyoung / Jaehyuk / Seeker / Junghwan]
[The Seeker enters the room Junghwan is in]
[The sound of the Seeker's approaching footsteps]
Found you.
[Found you, Junghwan!]
[Junghwan gets caught first]
Looks like they got someone.
[Fear-induced temporary pause]
[Jaehyuk heads towards the hallway to assess the situation]
[And comes face to face with the Seeker]
Ahhh!
Ahhhhh!
[Found you, Jaehyuk!]
[Doyoung witnesses Jaehyuk's capture]
[And quickly heads back inside]
I mean you already spotted me, so did you have to chase me down?
[(Airing his grievances)]
Seriously...
[Jeongwoo still hidden away on the 3rd floor]
What's going on?
Looks like Junghwan and Jaehyuk got caught.
Do I go in here?
Wow I
never thought I'd end up in jail.
[Padlocked shut / Jaehyuk and Junghwan are trapped in jail]
[Collect the keys to release the prisoners]
[Phone notification tone]
"Current remaining key count"
"Current remaining key count. One key in the basement"
"One on the 1st floor, two each on the 2nd, 3rd, and 4th floors"
This is the 2nd floor.
We need to...
[The last man standing on the 2nd floor]
Do we have to find keys while we're at it?
[On the hunt for keys / Asahi heads out carefully]
[But is promptly followed by the Seeker]
[The Seeker heads into the room Asahi just enetered]
[Found you, Asahi!]
[Jihoon and Haruto]
They said there are two keys on the 2nd floor.
We couldn't find them though. Where are they?
Let's start looking here.
We have to carry this team.
[Jihoon and Haruto's hiding spot / Is stumbled upon by Doyoung]
Someone's here.
[After a quick look around]
[He hides]
[The Seeker's footsteps sound pretty close]
[Jihoon and Haruto go back to their hiding spot]
[Thank goodness / The Seeker slips past Doyoug]
[Right when they all breathed a sigh of relief]
[Jihoon's phone rings]
[He quickly turns it off but]
[The Seeker is already heading back in their direction]
[The Seeker approaches Jihoon and Haruto but]
[Jihoon physically blocks the door]
[Now the Seeker heads for Doyoung]
[Eventually the Seeker moves on with nothing to show for it]
I actually saw the Seeker's face.
It was really scary-looking.
So scary.
I'm freaked out.
But right now, I really can't move.
Quiet, please.
[Jihoon's phone dings]
- Doyoung!
- Woah! What on earth?
Get in here.
You scared the life out of me.
Be quiet!
Turn the light off!
Why are you walking around with it on?
You totally startled me.
Keep your voice down!
[Jihoon's phone dings]
What's it say?
“Dude, it’s me Jaehyuk, 30 minutes left, save me.’”
[Jihoon responds right away]
[What's Jihoon's reply to Jaehyuk's plea?]
[okey-dokey, don't call me]
Pffft.
We should save him.
Well, we don’t have to, right?
I’m telling you, we do need to save him!
We have to save him.
Let's go to the fourth floor.
Okay.
Right now?
Now?
Yeah.
You mean we're heading up there now?
You guys are really brave.
[Junkyu / The Seeker's on the 1st floor]
[Junkyu notices too late]
No way!
[Found you, Junkyu!]
[Junkyu ends up in jail]
[Jailed Junghwan finds the phone numbers]
Hey, their phone numbers are here.
[He calls someone immediately]
[Do not enter / Danger zone / Phone rings loudly]
Hello?
Yoshi?
It's me, Junghwan.
Oh, Junghwan?
Dude, the Seeker got me.
Can I use this key to get you out?
I've actually got one.
Yeah, it'll work.
Okay.
I’ll come save you.
[Heading to jail / To save his buddy]
Guys?
Huh?
Who’s that?
It's Yoshi.
Yoshi, hey!
Who is that? Who’s there?
I’ve got a key.
Use it to save two people, man.
Jaehyuk, so you had a key!
[A short while ago, in jail]
Jaehyuk
[Before the game begun / Junkyu got a key from Doyoung thinking he was trapped]
I've actually got one key.
Yeah?
You can have it.
Who wants to go free?
Wait, can’t one key save multiple people?
No, no. It says right there.
It’s one per person.
Really?
That’s your key, so it’s yours for sure, Jaehyuk.
Who should I save?
Me! Me! Me! Save me!
I haven’t even done anything yet.
But Junghwan and Jaehyuk have been in here longer.
So let's save Junghwan, then?
I’ll come save you.
[Jaehyuk's prison break]
Be careful, Jaehyuk.
I’ll find two more keys and come back.
Yoshi! Yoshi!
You’d better run!
Run!
[Yoshi completes his mission and goes back into hiding]
[Junghwan's prison break]
I’ll go look for them.
Got it.
Come back safe.
Asahi, save us, please.
[Their game of hide and seek is halfway through]
[Phone dings]
[Junkyu / Asahi]
I just got a message.
Yeah?
The seeker is gone for a little while
and we get four minutes to hide even more thoroughly.
I got that too.
Yeah.
Where are the keys?
Seriously...
Why is there a camera here?
Woah...
I found one, everyone.
[The last key in the basement has been found]
Found one!
All right, I’m heading upstairs now.
See you later.
Guys!
Hey, guys!
Where are you guys?
Yoshi!
Dude, keep it down.
Shh!
We’ve still got four minutes though.
Huh?
We’ve got four minutes off from the game.
Man, I just saved two people.
I found one.
Really? In that case...
Yeah?
Over here.
[Yoshi leads Hyunsuk to the jail cells]
- What is it?
- Follow me.
Guys, Hyunsuk found one!
Guys!
Come on up, man.
Hey!
Hurry, hurry!
Hyunsuk, you've got to keep it down.
Over here.
[The gatekeeper]
Jeez, that was scary.
Careful, be careful.
Just say you found a key and
tell (the gatekeeper) who you’re saving.
Hyunsuk, who are you going to save?
Hang on, I need to check with the guys.
Guys?
[Hyunsuk's first time seeing his friends locked up]
Why’d you get caught?
Hyunsuk, did you figure out how this game's system works?
What? There's an actual system?
I was too busy hiding.
You should memorize the layout a bit.
Wait, I actually memorized the basement layout pretty well.
I’ll save you.
[Suddenly a sitcom]
I'll be sure to save you.
Many thanks.
You have my word.
You have my gratitude.
[Sitcom over]
I promised I'd save you.
Because he’s my
Japanese tomodachi, we
[Phone dings]
Whoa, that scared me.
[One minute till the Seeker returns / Here's a hint to help you find a key]
A cabinet?
It’s here, here.
Where is this place?
What is this?
Huh?
Over there.
Cross over, cross over.
Here?
They said there’s a key here.
Probably in that box.
So someone really was in here and came out.
Inside this box!
A box.
The box is here.
- Nice, nice.
- Nice.
They said it's in the box?
[The Seeker is back]
Ready or not, here I come
I’ll save Junkyu.
Shouldn’t we not save him yet?
[Junghwan heads inside the table the Seeker was in]
Don’t shut it! Don’t shut it!
Ready or not
Here I come
[On the 1st floor / Yoshi hides in a refrigerator]
Oh? A cabinet.
[In the midst of all this / Jaehyuk finds a key]
Is everyone hidden?
[Doyoung reclaims he Jaehyuk's old hiding spot]
Ready or not
Here
We
Come
Here we come
[Hide and seek with two Seekers]
Asahi.
Did you find one?
Found one.
[Jaehyuk rescues Asahi using the key he just found]
You found one, Jaehyuk!
Asahi, I found one.
Jaehyuk, for real?
Thank you.
I don’t have anyone left to save now.
Jaehyuk!
Hey! Run!
What? What's going on?
I heard a noise from the other side.
Is it the Seeker?
[A Seeker arrives on the 1st floor]
[Junkyu and Jaehyuk couldn't get far from jail]
[Asahi's hiding in jail]
[One Seeker wanders around close to Yoshi's spot]
[Takes a look in the refrigerator, then heads back out]
What the heck?
Let’s rest for a bit.
[There's still a Seeker on the 1st floor]
[Asahi leaves the jail in stealth mode]
I think they’re gone.
[Using their wits to assess the situation / Junkyu and Jaehyuk]
[Carefully head out]
[As they head across the 1st floor]
[The Seeker and Asahi]
Ahhh...
[Eventually cross paths]
[Found you, Asahi!]
[Clueless about Asahi's fate / Junkyu heads in the same direction]
[Eye witness]
[Assessing the situation]
[Junkyu's excited breathing]
What was that?
[Asahi winds up back in jail]
Even though we made eye contact
I’m wondering if I could’ve gotten away if I had run.
[The other Seeker on the 3rd floor]
They’re on this floor.
Yeah, hide.
[Seeker barges in before Jeongwoo can hide]
Time out, time out.
Time out, please.
I’m literally having heart failure... I swear.
Call 911, for real.
Wait, hang on.
Hang on, just a sec.
Hey! Wait!
Ah! Hey!
Hey! Wait! Hey!
Hey!
Dude, seriously!
Why were you running at me like that?
You nearly gave me a heart attack.
[Junghwan's breathing]
I almost died twice just now.
At least we found one key.
You don’t know where the others are locked up, right?
No idea. Where are they?
I know. They’re on the 1st floor.
First floor?
On the first floor.
Let’s go.
Okay, okay.
But there’s a bat over there, though.
[Grabs the baseball bat for now]
If someone shows up, we hide here right away.
[The 2nd floor hallway's in complete dissaray]
Let’s get out of here!
We can’t just stay. We have to move.
[Quiet sounds of the Seeker's footsteps]
Should we try going back?
Let’s go!
If they’re here, I’ll freak out.
No one here, we’re good.
Hang on.
Let’s head out now.
We can leave.
They make their footsteps loud on purpose.
Okay, let’s go.
No one’s here.
Let’s go.
[The three of them head back out]
[Someone lets out a horrifying shriek]
Hey, that sounded like Jaehyuk.
So Jaehyuk got caught again?
He’s been caught again.
[A little while earlier]
That scared me.
Seriously.
[Junkyu's headed back up to the 2nd floor]
[Hears the Seeker's footsteps for the umpteenth time]
[Looks around]
[And enters the cabinet]
No way. This door...
[The Seeker heads in the room Junkyu's in]
[Just as Junkyu narrowly avoids danger]
[Jaehyuk appears out of nowhere]
[Caught you, Jaehyuk!]
Woah! Ahhh!
[Yoshi flees without glancing back]
Jaehyuk
Woah.
Crazy.
That was terrifying.
This is insane.
I mean
getting ambushed like that...
Hey, Asahi, you all right?
It’s so unfair, being ambushed.
It’s my first time in here, actually.
Jeongwoo they got you?
Yeah, I got caught.
Woah this place is horrifying.
[Time left / 1,117 seconds]
[Number of prisoners / Three]
[Can they get them out in time?]
Guys
I’ll come save you.
Jihoon!
Yeah.
Let’s do this!
All right.
[These three are on their 3rd mission]
Where’s the jail?
Go right! Keep going right.
[The Seeker's footsteps sound far off]
[The boys escape]
[Running faster than they've ever run before]
[Returning to safety]
My legs are shaking.
So this is the third floor, and
Huh?
[Junkyu keeps looking for keys]
Just hang on please, I’ll stay here for a bit.
[After strolling through the halls]
[The Seeker ends up in Junkyu's hiding spot]
[Junkyu pretends not to see]
[Caught you, Junkyu!]
Ahhh!
Thank you.
Who is that? Junkyu?
Jeongwoo.
You got caught?
Why’d you get caught this time?
Asahi.
Hey there.
Jaehyuk.
Man, how’d you get caught?
Jeongwoo.
[Time left / 1,000 seconds]
[Key Location Hint]
Fourth floor recording room key storage.
[Junghwan found a key]
Found it, found it, found it!
[Senses a suspicious presence]
[Hyunsuk on the 3rd floor]
[Face check complete]
Nice!
Yo, Bro!
[They sense the Seeker]
[Hyunsuk slips into a room on the 3rd floor]
[Junghwan heads for the 1st floor]
[Checking the Key Location Hint while hiding]
[Rummaging through something]
Found it.
[Luckily found a key in his hiding spot]
I think Haruto’s dozing off somewhere, just sitting?
But where did Doyoung go?
Where did Junghwan go?
He gets the rules enough.
[Junghwan finds a key and heads straight to his jailed friends]
Junghwan.
Hey, I have a key too.
We can save two people.
Two?
[Before the Seeker shows up]
[Jeongwoo finds a key on the 3rd floor]
A key!
Save Jeongwoo and Asahi.
Jeongwoo and Asahi?
No, no, no! Save Jaehyuk!
No, no, no!
Please save Jeongwoo and Asahi.
We’re so close to death here.
Could you fix this for me?
Your bodycam broke?
It broke.
[The three leave their hide out / Once again]
Let’s head this way.
[The Seeker's footsteps]
[Doyoung running]
[He makes a safe return to his hiding spot]
[Doyoung and Haruto share a bitter laugh]
[Jihoon is by himself]
[With the key firmly in his grasp / He heads to the jail on the 1st floor]
Oh, it’s Yoshi.
- Yo, where’s the jail? The jail?
- This way.
[Yoshi leads Jihoon to the jail]
Oh? Hey, hey
Jihoon’s here.
Guys.
Guys, come save me!
Who can you save?
Save Junkyu. Save Junkyu.
- I’ll save Junkyu.
- Yeah, save Junkyu.
Jihoon!
Thank you.
[Phone dings]
Hey, it says a dark shadow is about to fall on someone.
What does that mean? What does it mean?
[With only 444 seconds left, a dark shadow will fall upon you]
[Open the jail on the 1st floor]
[Dark shadows head out in search of their victims]
[The shadows will stay till the game is over]
Run!
Run, run!
I’ll be right back, Jaehyuk.
What’s happening? Why are you coming out? What's going on?
Why are you coming out? Why?
Guys, someone just came out downstairs!
Downstairs!
What the heck?
What is that?
[Asahi's shadow]
Wait a second.
Darkness stuck to me.
Oh? It got on me too. Sorry.
Doesn’t this feel like Gonjiam?
[Taking refuge on the 2nd floor]
Who is that?
[Doyoung's shadow]
Aha!
After 444 seconds...
We got that text, remember?
It said a shadow would cling to us.
A shadow
latched onto us.
Creepy.
It’s literally a shadow.
So it’s stuck behind us?
Put it in front of you.
How do I stick it in front?
So if these guys get caught
does it mean we got caught too?
Because they're our shadows?
Possibly?
Dude, your shadow arrived.
[Half shadow, half person]
This is driving me crazy.
[Time left]
They say there’s a key in the second maze on the third floor.
We haven’t gone there?
No, no one has.
I’ll head up to the third floor.
Ah! You scared me!
Dude!
You freaked the shadow out.
Should we go to the third floor?
Can I be honest?
Yeah.
I really don’t want to go.
We can just find the key and go.
Hyunsuk!
I’m going to save Jaehyuk.
How’d you do that?
I found the third-floor key.
How’d you find it?
No idea. Just found it.
Using the clue?
I just ended up in the right room, I guess.
I wasn’t even praying or anything.
Let’s hide. All we have to do is hide now.
Let’s just hide.
But who were those people in black earlier?
I have no idea.
Is it over?
- I can’t find them, uh oh.
- It’s over.
It’s over.
I can’t find them, uh oh.
But this place was totally legendary.
At first, we were all suspicious of each other.
Right, right.
We even suspected Junkyu at first.
The entire game started because of him.
Seriously.
The moment he opened that box, the game started.
Doyoung basically kicked things off.
Yeah, I was the one who opened that box.
There was a ghost in there.
Like this.
Really?
And that’s how the game began.
Exactly.
I want to see the seeker at least once.
I never got to see them.
Seriously?
Not even once.
Let me read this, guys.
Hide and seek is over.
Check the target survival rate on your keys.
If TREASURE’s survival rate is above the target
there will be a big reward for Treasure Maker.
It feels like we can win any prize now, since it’s 100%.
We’re at 100%?
Everyone survived?
At the last minute, I saved Jaehyuk and we hit 100%.
We saved everyone.
I was so touched by Hyunsuk earlier.
He totally carried us, right?
Yeah, you really
carried us.
For real.
Since we hit 100%, that means
we can give a special gift back to Treasure Maker.
We’re at 100%! We’re at 100%!
One, two, three!
That was terrifying.
That was insane.